question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "hard",
     "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Pink Floyd&#039;s 1973 album &quot;Animals&quot; features a photograph of Battersea Power Station.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
     "question": "Deadpool&#039;s identity is Slade Wilson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Upwelling in the ocean provides colder nutrient rich water for plants and decomposers.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "In 2008, Usain Bolt set the world record for the 100 meters with one shoelace untied.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Liechtenstein does not have an airport.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
